listingsca.com 2019-02-25

# Privacy Policy - Listings Canada

## Privacy Policy

##### Information Collection and Use

LWorld Media Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. LWorld Media Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

##### Registration

In order to add links to this website, a user must first complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about updates and changes on our site that affect them, and verify user modifications to listings. 

##### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates (with the exception of classifieds and forums, in which cookies are used only to store user preferences and determine which messages are new since their last visit).

If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.   
To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).

##### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

##### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

##### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we [LWorld Media Inc.] are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

##### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please feel free to [contact us](http://listingsca.com/common/contact.asp).

##### Site and Service Updates

Occasionally, we will send registered users site and service announcement updates. We do not provide a way for registered users to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about our listings and related services. 

##### Correction/Updating/Deleting Personal Information:

All users have the option at any time of submitting corrections or updates to their listing registration information, or requesting such information to be deleted. We normally process such submissions on a weekly basis.

##### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email.  Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

* * *

Press the Back Button on your browser to return to the previous page.

This site is operated by 2019 [Cedar Lake Software](http://cedarlakesoftware.ca/)
